No, no, no. Don't feed the dog, darling.
Thanks, babe.
- You slept late.
- Yeah, I need to go.
What you got going today?
I've got to finish up some curtains
for Saturday,
and Nat and Cam are coming over.
- With the kids?
- Yeah.
Cammie said she just needed
to get out of the house.
Tell Nat to take it easy on her.
Cam can hold her own.
We need to send in the deposit
for the beach condo.
I love you.
- Just write the check, babe, okay?
- Okay. Bye.
No more food.
You, eat.
Yeah, let's keep going with that bit.
It'll go another 10 feet.
We won't get the gravel pack down today.
Why not?
Clouds.
We're gonna have to call it.
Happy hour starts at 5:00, Dewart.
Not if it's raining.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
They were just drinking and laughing
And, oh, my God,
it was like I was being in a museum
and I saw the progress from apes to men.
I saw it. I saw the future.
Dewart, that was him,
that was going to be him in 20 years.
Let me tell you, you laugh.
You laugh. But this little one in your arms is
gonna be shuffling in a bar just like them.
- Yep.
- No.
Don't listen to her.
- Hannah!
- What?
- You guys okay?
- Yeah.
No. Don't touch.
You understand?
Okay. Come here.
Go play.
Hey, DJ. Bring the girls inside.
What?
- It's not my fault. I told you.
- Yeah, all right.
All right, I'm calling it. Shut it down.
- Bye, guys. Thank you for coming.
- I'll call you about the Lions Club supper.
- Okay. Love you.
- Bye, Sam.
BYE, Cam!
Can you sign
S-T-O-R-M?
Storm.
I gotta get home.
Nat and me been looking into a threesome.
We've been chatting with this girl online
from Canton.
Yeah. Big old girl.
What's big?
She's about 250, 275.
She can't be no taller than five foot.
Shit, man.
I don't see me and Sam
getting into something like that.
No. I don't guess you would.
You got a good life, Curtis.
I'm serious.
I think that's the best compliment
you can give a man,
take a look at his life
and say, "That's good.
"That guy's doing something right."
Well, it ain't always so easy.
Hell, I know that.
Shit. I gotta go.
Good night.
Hey, baby.
She do all right today?
She was fine.
She's still not playing
with the others, though.
She can't connect.
Honey, you gotta clean up that trash pile
in the back.
She fished out a
board that had nails on it.
I'll get to it this weekend.
I still take off my boots,
so I won't wake her up.
I still whisper.
Curtis?
- What?
- Did you hear me?
You got to be home, showered,
ready to walk out the door by 6:00 tonight.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I just want her to eat her breakfast
and stop playing with the damn dog.
She's fine down there.
She had toast already.
- All right.
- What?
Hannah. Come here. Hannah.
- Curtis?
- What?
I'm late.
- You didn't eat anything.
- It's okay.
I didn't say you had control
over the weather, Russell.
What I did say was that the top shelf
has got to be cleared by the 15th.
That's non-negotiable.
Curtis?
Curtis? Where we at on that East 82nd site?
Yesterday slowed us down.
We couldn't get the second pilot hole drilled.
It rained for two hours yesterday.
Two hours,
and our entire schedule went in the toilet?
We lose the permit
if you're not out of there, end of day.
- Yes, sir.
- End of day, Curtis.
All right. Valerie tells me
that the father-son pancake cook-off...
Hey, I gotta make a stop
before we head out there.
- Think we got time?
- Yeah, there's time.
Shit.
Son of a bitch.
- We stripped that bit.
- Yeah.
Well, bring it up. We gotta reset it.
Curtis!
- You ever see birds fly like that?
- What?
Damn it.
Come on, we gotta go.
Jesus.
Honey, I can really use a shower.
Hi.
So if you continue with
the basic vocabulary,
this will allow you to communicate
with your children better.
Between the ages of four and seven,
the focus is more on the sign.
And then later,
we'll begin adding the alphabet
as more of a support system.
Now, in ASL, the male sign is
signed at the forehead area.
For example, "father,"
is signed up here like this.
Father. Very good.
- You're not sorry.
- I am sorry.
Well, you stink. You smell really bad.
I think I smell good.
Do I smell good?
See? Maybe I should marry her instead.
Stop.
Man.
You okay?
Shit!
You're okay.
It's okay.
No!
Hannah!
Here, honey. Put on your shoes.
- Good, you're up.
- Yeah.
Honey, you're soaked.
I've felt better.
I guess we can stay home if we need to.
Where you going?
It's Saturday.
I was going to take Hannah to my booth.
Yeah.
You look really sick, honey.
I'm all right.
It's just a cold or something.
Let me get you some Advil.
No. Don't worry about it.
Just go. I'll be fine.
You sure?
Better already.
Okay. I got my phone if you need anything.
Don't forget, Sunday
lunch is here tomorrow.
If you're sick, we should cancel.
I'll be all right.
Okay, we'll talk later.
Come on. Let's go.
- You sure?
- Honey, please.
How much you asking for this pillow?
This pillow is $15.
That's more than I want to spend.
This is all hand stitched.
It takes a really long time.
That's why I charge that.
I'll give you $7 for it.
I can't go that low.
Well, that's my offer.
How about 10?
I'll give you $8, but it's in change.
That's fine.
Lucky for you she likes to count change.
Red.
Come on.
Get in. Good boy.
I'm sorry about this, buddy.
We just gotta work it like this
for a while, okay?
While rescue workers made several
attempts to reach the family,
- Walter Jacobs' wife and brother-in-law died.
- That's what I don't understand.
If he didn't do anything,
why did you put him out back?
What?
Did you hear me?
I said if he didn't do anything,
why did you have to put him outside?
I just wanted him to be
outside for a while.
He's your dog.
He's always been an inside dog.
He's my dog, that's why he's outside.
Look,
right now with Hannah and everything,
I just think it'd be better.
- Hannah loves Red.
- Hold on.
The gas cloud spread across
their six-acre property.
The only way off their land
was across the train tracks,
which were blocked by wreckage.
I tried using some wet rags
and some towels to breathe through,
but that just seemed
to make it worse.
While rescue workers made several
attempts to reach the family,
Walter Jacobs' wife and
brother-in-law died in the home.
Jacobs survived despite enduring 11
hours of exposure to the gas cloud...
You hearing this?
It's awful.
Eleven hours.
No way out.
Hannah.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
- Babe?
- Yeah?
You got the number for Dr. Shannan?
You're still not feeling good?
Yeah, we got the number?
Yeah, baby, but he'll be closed today.
Right. Yeah, I'll call tomorrow.
Honey, if you're not feeling good,
- we got to take you...
- No. Stop!
Okay.
Do you want me to cancel lunch today?
Shit.
- What is that?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I just...
I got a sore throat.
I'm sorry I'm taking it out on you.
I was gonna leave Hannah with you
so I could go to church,
but I'm not gonna with you like this.
It's fine. I'll be fine.
- No. She needs breakfast.
- I got it.
I'm sorry that you feel bad,
but you need to drop the attitude.
Come on. Just go.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just go.
Hannah's in the den.
We have cereal for her.
We're going out.
We're going out. Okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
You stay put, okay?
Let's just start.
Let's all join hands for the blessing.
- Where the hell have you been?
- I know. I'm sorry. I had to run an errand.
- You're really late.
- I know.
You didn't even bring your cell phone.
Missed you at church this morning, Curtis.
Dad.
He knows what to do
if he wants me to stop asking.
Was it a good service?
It was. It was good work.
I'm thinking about cleaning up
that storm shelter out back.
Curtis?
- Curtis, how you doing, bud?
- Hey, Doc.
- How's my girl?
- She's good.
That's good to hear.
Tilt your head back for me.
I don't have a cold.
- Did she get that down wrong?
- No, I just told her that.
So what's the problem?
I've been having...
I've been having some trouble sleeping.
I was hoping
you could give me something for it.
How long's this been going on?
About four nights now.
You're not sleeping at all?
Well, some, but real restless.
Well, I think four nights
is a little too soon to tell.
My advice would be to not eat
or drink anything after 8:00 at night.
Cut back on any alcoholic drinks,
tobacco, caffeine.
Get some daily exercise.
Well, I think...
- I think I might need to try some medication.
- Why do you say that?
The reason I've been having trouble
sleeping is these dreams I've been having.
I didn't think it was anything at first,
but then the other day I woke up
and the bed was wet.
- You urinated in your bed?
- Yeah.
Couple days before that,
I had a dream that my dog attacked me
and it took all day
for the pain in my arm to go away.
You been out to see your mother lately?
It's been about a month.
Okay.
Okay. This is a prescription
for a pretty mild sedative.
It's non-habit forming,
but I'm only giving you enough
for a few days anyway.
Take it and see if it helps.
In the meantime,
this is the number of a good friend of mine
in Columbus. He's a psychiatrist.
It's a drive, but he's the best I know.
Okay.
I'll give him a call
and let him know you'll be down to see him.
All right.
- Hey, Dewart.
- What you say, Curtis?
Not much.
They want us
to get a pilot hole drilled by lunch.
I figure worse comes to worse,
we can eat on the rig.
Yeah, we'll get it done. Weekend all right?
Yeah. Same old shit.
No. No, I need the name of the specialist
whose diagnosis you'll accept.
No. Look it, I've told you this twice.
Please.
Just get me the name
and/or the approval code.
Okay.
All right. And the phone? All right.
Great. Well, thank you very much.
All right, this is the name
and the phone number of the specialist
who the insurance company approves of.
Just call and make an appointment.
Now if this doctor signs off,
you should have the implant procedure
fully covered.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Can I give you a hug?
It's fine. It's fine.
You know, your husband's company actually
has very good insurance when it kicks in.
Not a lot of jobs offer policies half
as good. You're very lucky.
That's okay.
We have your insurance on file.
- That'll be $47.64.
- What's the co-pay?
That is your co-pay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you too.
I have good news.
Green? How about a red?
It was like talking to a
sane person for once.
She made one phone call. That's it.
I've been trying that 800 number
for weeks. You.
It's great. It's great.
Hey, Hannah.
Are you excited?
We're gonna get you some help.
How do you say, sign, "excited"?
Like this.
Excited? Yeah?
All right. What've we got here?
I got to do you.
Honey, look at this one.
It's a 2-1, and it sits
directly on the beach.
Wouldn't that be great? We wouldn't have
to worry about Hannah crossing traffic.
- What's the rent?
- $899 a week.
That sounds real nice.
You sleep well?
Yeah. I did.
You look like you're feeling better.
You want me to come up there
and do it for you?
Jesus.
Hey, how much food you think you'd need
to live on for a week?
- What do you mean?
- I mean to stay alive.
What do you think you'd need?
- Not a lot.
- Yeah? You think?
I don't know.
You hear about people living for days
all the time off bark and melted snow.
I've never heard of that.
Shit, I don't know. You asked the question.
It's on there.
It's on. Come on.
Damn it.
What?
It sounds like thunder.
What sounds like thunder?
What's the matter with you, Curtis?
Curtis?
Where you going? Curtis, where you going?
- Curtis.
- Hey, Mom.
- Come in.
- Sure.
I'm gonna get some water.
You want some?
No.
Isn't she lovely?
- Mom?
- Yes?
I need to ask you something.
Do you remember what year
we brought you up here?
To the first place.
It was '86.
Yes. Because Kyle was going to be a senior.
- I was 10.
- Yes.
Can you remember what happened
before you got diagnosed?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
I just want to know how it all started.
Before you had to leave.
I don't know.
I remember it was a real stressful time.
Your father was gone a lot,
and I couldn't handle things on my own.
Did you ever have any
dreams?
Like, bad dreams?
No. Nothing like that.
There was always...
There was always a panic
that took hold of me.
I thought people were watching me
and listening to me.
It's all right. It's fine.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm fine.
May I have the number
for Dr. George Shannan?
Thanks.
Hi, is Dr. Shannan there?
May I speak with him?
This is Curtis LaForche.
Hey, Doc.
Yeah, sorry... Sorry to call you at home.
I just... I don't think I can make it
to Columbus to see that psychiatrist.
Yeah, it's just too far.
Is there somewhere local
you could send me?
Hey.
Sorry I woke you up.
It's okay.
Where you been?
I went to see Mom.
Is she okay?
Yeah. I just wanted to check up on her.
You should've told me,
we would have gone with you.
No, that's okay.
Come to bed.
I will in a bit.
Well, you've kept up with the payments
on the house.
We've been good about that.
I gotta tell you, Curtis, banks aren't
loaning money the way they used to.
We've got you a loan today,
but the interest rates are variable.
We have to tie it to your house.
That's fine.
Curtis, I've known you a long time.
Financed your house for you, two vehicles.
I'm telling you,
this is a risky loan you're taking.
I need the money, John.
Okay.
- Hey.
Sorry I left you yesterday.
- Jim came by. I covered for you.
- Thanks.
- I need your help with the depth charts.
- Sure.
Fucking Nat put me in charge of frying
oysters for that Lions Club supper.
You need another burner?
Yeah, if you still got
yours, I could use it.
Hey, you think you could help me
with something?
What do you need?
I'm gonna build out the tornado shelter
in my backyard. I could use some help.
The hell you wanna do that for?
Just needs to be done.
What do you need?
I figure I'll do it on a Saturday,
borrow some equipment from work.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah, I just need a backhoe, a hauler.
I'll rent the rest.
- Yeah. Whatever. I'll help.
- Thanks.
- You all right, man?
- What do you mean?
I just don't wanna see you fuck up.
I'm not.
Come in.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Have a seat. I'm Kendra.
- Curtis.
Okay.
I'm gonna start
by asking you some questions.
Okay. I already answered
all the questions on the form.
Yeah, I know. I looked at them,
but I need to get a profile started on you.
Right. Well...
Out of the five possible symptoms
needed to be diagnosed with schizophrenia,
delusions, hallucinations,
disorganized speech,
disorganized behavior
and the negative symptoms,
I've had two.
Delusions and hallucinations.
So, I took this quiz in
the back of the book.
I scored a five out of a possible 20.
Schizophrenia starts at 12. So...
They say it might be
a brief psychotic disorder.
Yeah. Whatever it is,
I need to know what to do
or what to get on
to get this thing under control.
Look. I'm a counselor.
Certified, but I'm not a psychiatrist.
I can't prescribe anything to you.
I can talk to you,
I can recommend where to send you,
but that's it.
Now, that said, if you
want to talk, I'll listen.
For a lot of people, that's a good start.
Now you said here
that your mother was diagnosed
with paranoid schizophrenia in her 30s.
And you're at 35.
You wanna talk about that?
Yeah, I don't know my mother's symptoms.
I was just 10.
My brother was 17. And...
I don't know. She just left me in the car
in the parking lot
at the grocery store one day.
And she didn't come back.
And then they found her a week later
eating trash out of a dumpster
in Northern Kentucky.
My dad had to put her
in the State Hospital in Columbus.
And she's been in assisted
living ever since.
Yep.
My dad raised me.
He died last April.
So tell me about these dreams.
I don't know what our
schedule will be, but...
That's all right.
But I really do think you should
continue with the sign language.
And any additional therapies
that kids need for the cochlear implant.
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
- Good night.
Is anyone seeing this?
Hey.
It's all right. Calm down, okay?
- Samantha?
- Are you out of your mind?
Not a word.
You didn't say one word about this to me.
Don't you think you owe me that?
Don't you think that you might
respect me enough
to at least consider what I'd have to say?
I didn't want you worrying about it.
Well, I'm worried, Curtis.
How are you paying for all that?
I got a home improvement loan
from the bank.
How could you do that
without talking to me?
You know the expenses we have coming up.
You want to waste money
on a stupid tornado shelter?
I'm doing it... I'm doing it for us.
I know you don't understand.
You're right. I don't understand.
I don't understand half the stuff
you've been doing lately.
I don't understand you
putting Red out back.
I don't understand
you staying up all night
in that stupid tornado shelter.
You don't come to bed half the time.
You leave, you don't tell me
where you're going. Explain that to me.
Please.
Tell me something
that helps me understand
why you're being like this.
There's nothing to explain.
I'm gonna go put Hannah to bed.
Curtis?
Baby. Oh, my God. Baby...
Oh, my God. Baby.
I need an ambulance!
My husband's having a seizure.
41800 Tindale Road.
Hurry up. He's bleeding!
Okay.
Honey?
Honey? Are you okay?
You were having a seizure.
I called an ambulance.
No. It's fine. It's fine.
Don't send an ambulance.
- What are you doing?
- It's fine.
Ma, am?
Baby, what's going on?
I'm sorry you fellows had to come
all the way out.
It's what we do.
Now we can still take you in
if you want a doctor
to look at those cuts in your mouth.
Yeah, that's all right.
I'll see somebody on Monday.
All right.
Thanks.
I haven't been honest with you.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
I've been having these dreams.
I guess they're more like nightmares.
It's why I've been acting like this.
They...
They always start with a kind of storm.
Like a real powerful storm.
And there's always
this dark, thick rain.
Like fresh motor oil.
And then the things,
people, it just makes them crazy.
They attack me. Sometimes...
Sometimes they go after Hannah.
First one I had,
Red nearly chewed through my arm.
That's why you put him out back?
Yeah.
What was the dream? Tonight.
It was Dewart.
We were at the job site.
The storm started and something happened.
His face...
His eyes were
different.
He came after me with a pickax.
And we fought.
And he ran it through my leg.
It's hard to explain,
because it's not just a dream.
It's a feeling.
I'm afraid something might be coming.
Something that's
not right.
I cannot describe it.
I just need you to believe me.
I've been to a counselor.
I've seen her...
I've seen her a few times.
You know what I come from.
And I promised myself...
I promised myself I would never leave.
And I am doing everything that I can
to make that true.
Okay, since the doctor's approved
her surgery,
we just need to get her scheduled.
The next possible opening
is the 21st of next month.
That's six weeks.
- Six weeks?
- Is that okay?
It's wonderful.
This point just to the west.
I don't think we'll have any problem
We should be able to get 20,
maybe 30 in this next week.
But we're looking to see
how that's gonna shape up, so...
- Curtis?
- Yeah.
- What do you think?
- Yeah. That sounds good.
We'll get it done.
Come in.
What you need, Curtis?
- I need a favor, Jim.
- What's that?
Can you take Dewart off my crew?
Just reassign him someplace else.
What's the trouble?
He not pulling his weight?
No, nothing like that. He's a good worker.
He's a good man. He's my friend.
I think it'd be easier not being in
charge of someone I'm so close to.
You know, I understand.
This is part of what it means
to manage people, Curtis.
You're gonna have to learn that.
Yes, sir. I appreciate that, but...
Well, it would just be
very helpful in this case.
Okay.
Well, I can put him with Russell.
- Anybody else you'd prefer?
- No. Whoever you think's right.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
You been missing a lot of work, Curtis.
I know.
My daughter's had a lot of doctor's visits.
I haven't let anything get behind.
No. But don't. Okay?
Yes, sir.
I know they just usually
do oysters and fries,
but what if we did
something healthier on the side?
What, like 'slaw?
I don't know. Maybe a vegetable or salad.
Dewart's been telling me
how strange Curtis has been acting lately.
I am so sorry.
It's not like you don't have
enough on your plate with Hannah.
Things are fine.
We're fine.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
- Can I look at one of these gas masks?
- Sure.
Which one you want to look at?
The newest one.
- How much?
- $178.
Anything cheaper?
No. That's the cheapest
one I got in the store.
They go all the way up to $290.
I don't know what you want to spend,
but a gas mask ain't something
you want to go cheap on.
You got any kids' sizes?
No.
Kids can't wear those.
They gotta have a special thing,
it's like a hood.
I don't fool with those.
What the hell are you doing?
What you got going on here?
I'm just adding on to the storm shelter.
- Why?
- Just because.
You running water to it?
Yeah. From our well.
Running sewer out to the city line.
How much you spending on this thing?
- It's not bad.
- Doesn't look it.
You take your eye off the ball
one minute in this economy
and you're screwed.
- You got the cash for this?
- Yeah.
Don't put nothing on credit cards.
That shit'll eat you up.
I'm not.
Samantha called me.
I figured.
Called you to come tell me to quit?
She called 'cause she's worried.
Says you've been stressed out.
- So?
- So what?
You stressed out?
No. No more than anybody else.
Work all right?
Hey, look. You wanna come by and
have dinner sometime, Kyle? That's fine.
We'll have a beer and
talk about the old days,
but you got something to say, just say it.
You can stop that shit right now.
I'll come over there and remind you
what it's like to get your ass whipped.
I'm just coming here to check on you.
Well, I appreciate it, Kyle.
You been to see Mom?
Yeah. A few days ago.
She all right?
You should see her.
Take your girls.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll get around to it.
- You need a hand?
- No. I've got it.
Okay.
- Call me if you need me, okay?
- I will.
Hey, Kyle?
Actually, you could do me a favor.
- What's that?
- You still looking for a dog?
Sure.
They got a good spot for you, okay, buddy?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I know it'll make my girls happy.
All right.
- Hey, Kyle?
- Yeah?
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
All right. All right.
I will, little brother.
You take care of your family.
Handle your business. Okay?
All right. Bedtime.
You okay?
Who's that?
Shit.
Hey, Jim.
Curtis.
Dewart told me you took equipment
from work for a project at your house.
Said that's why
you wanted him off your crew.
I came out here to see it myself.
Yeah. It was just a hauler and a backhoe.
It was Saturday.
I had them back in less than eight hours.
You know that doesn't matter.
I can't even tell you
how many rules you broke.
What if you had an accident? Huh?
What if you ran somebody over
on your way out here?
Lawsuit like that could bankrupt me.
Well,
I'm sorry, Jim. I hadn't thought of that.
Thank God nothing like that happened,
you know?
I'll do whatever I can to make it right.
You can pick up your last check on Friday.
You've got two weeks' benefits.
Did you fire Dewart, too?
He's on two weeks leave, unpaid.
I'm sorry, Curtis.
You did this to yourself.
Damn.
I've been fired.
What about the health insurance?
We get two more weeks.
I'm sorry.
- Excuse me.
- Are you Curtis?
- Yeah.
- Come in.
Kendra transferred out.
I'll be meeting with you today.
Please, sit down.
What happened to Kendra?
She got into a program at OSU,
so she'll be transferring near there.
I've split her caseload
with another counselor.
It's been kind of crazy around here lately.
So,
I've looked over your file.
It says your mother was diagnosed
with paranoid schizophrenia
in her early 30s.
Let's start there.
I'm so sorry. I completely forgot.
That's okay. Don't worry about it.
- Thanks.
- Here. I hope you like them.
- I brought cash.
- That's terrific. It's fine.
Call me if they don't work
and I'm sorry again.
It's okay. Thank you.
Okay. All done. Done.
Sweet dreams.
What's that?
That's the alternator from the truck.
I was just trying to figure out a way
to charge enough batteries
to run lights down there.
Yeah, what the hell.
Maybe I'll hook it up to your old Exercycle.
You gonna leave me?
You flinched
when I touched your hand this morning.
I'm sorry.
I was in one of your dreams?
Yeah.
Can you deal with that?
Okay. Then I made a decision.
We cancel the beach trip.
We have enough to cover bills for
the next two months with your last check.
I'm going to get a job.
You're gonna find another job.
I'm going to call to see
if we can move Hannah's surgery up.
We'll need to see what it costs to
extend your policy to the end of the year.
I want you to see a psychiatrist.
Not a counselor from the free clinic.
Someone good.
Dr. Shannan gave me
the number of somebody,
but I just don't think we can afford it.
We'll find the money.
Also, the Lions Club supper's this weekend.
I want you to come with me.
I don't want to see any of those people.
I want you to go.
I need to do something normal.
All right.
- How many pieces does Hannah get?
- Just one.
What're you doing here?
Not here, man.
I said, what are you doing here?
Curtis?
I've told people what you've been doing.
I know.
You cut me loose.
Everything we been through.
I know. I'm sorry.
- Hey, hey.
- You ain't fucking sorry.
- All right.
You sorry, you wouldn't cut me loose.
We're fucking friends!
This how you treat friends?
Come on.
God damn it.
Stop it, Dewart!
Fuck!
I said not here!
God damn it!
You think I'm crazy?
Is that what he told you?
Well, listen up!
There is a storm coming
like nothing you have ever seen!
And not a one of you is prepared for it!
You think I'm crazy?
Hey, I'm talking to you, Russell!
Lewis! You think I'm a thief?
Sleep well in your beds.
Because if this thing comes true,
there ain't gonna be any more.
Hannah?
Hannah!
Curtis? Wake up! Wake up!
Come on. It's okay.
It's okay.
See?
All right. Come on. Sit down.
All right.
Okay, honey, here you go.
- No. Don't do that.
- It's okay. It's oxygen.
Here. Put this on.
- Are you kidding?
- Please, just do it.
Okay?
There we go.
All right.
Keep it out of your eyes. Okay?
Hey. I love you. It's okay.
All right? All right. Okay.
Wake up, babe.
Where's your mask?
We took them off. It's fine.
- No.
- Take it off.
No.
We're fine.
Take it off.
You need to open the door now.
What if it's...
What if it's not over?
What?
It's over.
Get the keys.
Open the door.
It's still storming.
No. It's not.
I can hear it.
I don't hear anything.
Put your hand on the door. You can feel it.
Thunder? Do you feel it?
You feel it?
I'm sorry.
Baby, there's no storm outside.
Curtis, I wouldn't lie to you.
We love you very much.
Please
open the door.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I love you, but if I open the door,
then nothing's gonna change.
You'll see that everything's fine,
but nothing will change.
Please.
This is what it means to stay with us.
This is something you have to do.
Could you move Hannah back?
It's fine.
Do you have any vacation time
that you can use?
I don't have a job right now.
Well, I know that times are hard,
but I think it's really important
for you to separate yourself
from that storm shelter.
I think you need to break away
from it for a while.
We can start you on some medication
that I think will help,
but that action alone would mean a lot.
We usually go on a trip
to Myrtle Beach each summer.
We were gonna go this month.
I think that would be okay
if we start the medication now.
And it would give you all some time
to prepare as a family.
But I want to be clear,
when Curtis gets back,
he'll need to take more time than that.
What does that mean?
I mean that he'll need
hands-on therapy at a real facility.
You mean I have to leave my family?
I think you need to
seriously commit to some treatment.
Hey...
Good, huh?
Okay.
There we go.
Let's make a river.
Good. Yeah.
We put a top on it.
What is it, honey?
What?
Sam.
Okay.